[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James Gandolfini"]}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "Dan, what is the latest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "Well, we've been piecing together the tragic final minutes of James Gandolfini's life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Italy"]}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "What has been the reaction in Rome and Italy why -- to his death?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "WRB", ":", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "Yes, I mean, I think it's best to say he was not the kind of blockbuster star that he was in the States here in Italy.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Rome", "Italy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Well, that's the jury that was chosen, and I do think that that's where the decision is going to be made.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amanda Knox"]}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Because it seems that they're relying, the judge is, who called them back, on a theory that the original reason for what happened was a sex game gone wrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "They are but just to cut to the chase here, if I am Amanda Knox, I am going to go exactly nowhere.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "And, Gloria, I was a bit struck by the fact that they're clearly very, very lovey-dovey in one those images, suggesting perhaps they're even back together, but regardless of that from a legal point of view, how sensible is it that they are seen like this together when they've just been ordered back to court?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "Well, I don't know if they knew that a photo was being taken.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gloria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Italy"]}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Is there any part of the legal process that can force her to go back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Well, again, if they to extradite her perhaps but I had a case in Italy a number of years ago and frankly I don't have a whole lot of confidence in the Italian legal process.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "How can you not tell me about this before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Was that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "No, it was absolutely the opposite.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Now what does this do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "Well, this watch, I saw it a long time ago on somebody's hand at a computer show and explained to me, when you see it -- when I turned my wrist, hours, minutes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBN", "VBG", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "VBP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "What are those?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "These are old vacuum tubes called mixing tubes running on high voltage, 140 volts inside and even though it's waterproof I wouldn't take it in the bath and expect to live.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "RB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Is that legal tender?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "It's -- well, let me tell you, a lot of things about it are kind of fishy and hold it on the corners so you don't get the ink on your hands.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 249, "question": "And they come in pads all of eight, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "CD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$5"]}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "$", "CD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "What would you sell the eight for that's worked before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "All over the world I've sold them for $5 a sheet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$5"]}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "$", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "So you would -- you would sell me $8 worth for $5?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "$", "CD", "JJ", "IN", "$", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Yes, four of these bills for $5.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$8", "$5"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Why would I not just buy this entire pad now and make an immediate 100 bucks?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "Because there's so many other people around, I want to spread the joy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Are you -- are you a fan of somebody like Edward Snowden?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Yes, I'm not going -- you know, there are some people that takes sides in the world and I'm always against anything government, you know, any three-letter agency or I'm always for them because I'm on the opposite side, and I'm not like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Edward Snowden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Given the speed with which technology is advancing all the time, smart phones, computers, laptops, and so on, where are we going to be in 10 years' time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "The computer is going to get smarter and smarter, and more like humans.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Sweet little baby?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "As far as you can tell.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Do you know the baby's name?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "I do not know the baby's name.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "They were married?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "No, they're not married.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Will you come back soon and do a longer interview?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "I sure would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "Will you come back soon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "Yes, any time, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "So why has Wall Street gone into complete panic mode?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Because Wall Street like to -- they have this thing where you sell a news and you buy on the fear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Is there -- is there any sensible rationale for what Wall Street did today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "No, I --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "EX", "VBZ", ":", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Or is it simply taking a bit of money because they are greedy pigs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "YSSDAL: There's -- well, all right, your phrase.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Abby Huntsman, have you got anything to say about the global economy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Abby Huntsman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "RB", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Do you feel that the fact that someone like him has done this is indicative of just a sea change now coming through America quite quickly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "I think it's coming, and the only question is how quickly people are going to get out of the way when it does.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "And your positioning yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "I'm positioning myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBD", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "What was going through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Honestly nothing, just kept -- if the baby falls I just need to try to catch him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "WRB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Are you going to stand there and try and catch that baby knowing that one false move and it could die?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "It's so different reading the story and then putting it on prospective when you see exactly how far the baby fell.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "I'd like to think with four kids I would do what she did but I've got to say it was an extraordinarily brave thing to do, wasn't it, Marc?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "ILL: It was incredibly brave.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marc"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 649, "question": "These are the mom from the kid on the balcony?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "Are you kidding me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "We now have several states in America have legalized marijuana.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marc Lamont Hill"]}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "Cameras on or cameras off?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "Marc Lamont Hill, let me ask you one quick question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas", "Utah"]}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "In 30 years' time will there be any state in America which still outlaws marijuana?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "Probably Texas and Utah just because they're weird.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "I -- it really was a trail blazer, \"The Sopranos,\" wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "``", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 733, "question": "If heaven exist, what would you like to hear God say when you arrive at the pearly gates?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 734, "answer": "Take over for a while, I'll be right back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]